Guide to the Jesse Simons Papers WAG.044
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series II: Arbitration Decisions, undated
  - Paper Handlers' and Sheet Straighteners' Union, #1 v. Daily News, undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Pearl River Teachers' Association v. Pearl River Board of Education, undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Penn Central Co. v. Transport Workers' Union, undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Penn Central Co. v. United Transportation Union, undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Personnel Review Board, New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation, Decisions 1-289, Summaries 1-260, 1971-1982 (Box 9)
  - Petroleum Trades Employees Union v. Mobil Oil Corp., undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Petroleum Trades Employees Union v. Texaco, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Portsmouth Naval Shipyard v. Portsmouth Metal Trades Council, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Preferred Distributors, Inc. v. IBT, Local 46, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Price Brothers Co. v. IBT, Local 445, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Printing Pressman and Offset Workers Union, Local 51 v. American Metal Market, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union, #447 v. Paper Merchants Association of New York, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Providence Newspaper Printing Pressman's Union, #12 v. Edward A. Sherman Publishing, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Provision Salesmen and Distributors Union, Local 627 v. Hebrew National Kosher Foods, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Radio and Television Broadcast Engineers Union, Local 1212 v. Home Box Office, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Radio and Television Broadcast Engineers Union, Local 1212 v. WPIX, Inc., undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Realty Advisory Board of Labor Relations v. Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Locals 32B and 32J (25 cases), undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Retail Clerks International Union, Local 888 v. Florsheim Shoe Store, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Retail Clerks International Union, Local 1500 v. H.C. Bohack Co., undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Retail, Wholesale, and Chain Store Food Employees Union, Local 338 v. Great Atlantic and Pacific tea Company, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers' Union, Local 65 v. Leo Beckman, Inc., undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers' Union, Local 1-S v. Macy's New York, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers' Union, Local 1-S v. Macy's Northeast, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Robbins, Mary S. v. Trans World Airlines Inc., undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Rockland Community College Federation of Teachers, Local 1871 v. Rockland Community College, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Rodis, Katina v. Arden Hill Hospital, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Roslyn Teachers Association v. Roslyn Union Free School District, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Schalmont Teachers Association v. Schalmont Central School District Board of Education, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Seaboard Coastline Railroad Co. v. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Security and Law Enforcement Council #82 (AFSCME) v. NY State Department of Correctional Services (6 cases), undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Security and Law Enforcement Council #82 (AFSCME) v. NY State Department of Mental Health, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Security and Law Enforcement Council #82 (AFSCME) v. NY State Department of Mental Hygiene, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Local 144 v. AAA Maintenance, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - SEIU, Local 144 v. Association of Private Hospitals, Inc., undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - SEIU, Local 32-E v. Concourse Village, Inc., undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - SEIU, Local 144 v. Doctor's Hospital (3 cases), undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - SEIU, Local 155 v. Exterminating Industry Institute, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - SEIU, Locals 32B and 32J v. Rochdale Village, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - SEIU, Local 144 v. St. Mary's Hospital, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - SEIU, Local 200 v. Syracuse University, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - SEIU, Local 144 v. Wartburg Orphan Farm School, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Social Service Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 v. New York City Office of Labor Relations, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Shenendehowa Teachers' Association v. Shenendehowa Central School District, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Shopmen's Local Union #455 v. Dayton Metal Products, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Springfield Newspapers Employees Association v. Republican Company, undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - State of Connecticut Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities v. AFSCME, Council 4, undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - SUNY College of Brockport v. United University Professions, Inc., undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Synergy Gas Co. v. Sasso, Robert (IBT, Local 282) (1 of 3), undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Synergy Gas Co. v. Sasso, Robert (IBT, Local 282) (2 of 3), undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Synergy Gas Co. v. Sasso, Robert (IBT, Local 282) (3 of 3), undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Syracuse City Employee Local Union #400 v. City of Syracuse, New York, undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Teamsters and Chauffeurs union, Local 456 v. Handy Rent All, Inc., undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Telephone Traffic Union v. New York Telephone Co., undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Textile Workers Union of America, Local 3 v. Schlegel Corp., undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc. v. Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (7 cases), undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Transit Workers Union (TWU), Local 241 v. Columbia University, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - TWU, Local 553 v. Eastern Airlines (2 cases), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - TWU, Local 225 v. Gray Line New York Tours, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - TWU, Local 225 v. Hudson Transit Lines, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - TWU v. Penn Central Transportation Co. (2 cases), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Transportation Communications Union v. Southern Pacific Lines, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (TBTA) v. AFSCME, D.C. 37, Local 1931, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - TBTA Superior Officers Benevolent Association v. TBTA, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Ulysses Co. v. Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE), Local 231 v. Fashionland, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - UNITE, Local 310 v. Liz Claiborne, Inc. (4 cases), undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Union Trustees of the District 15 Machinists Pension Fund v. Employer Trustees of the District 15 Machinists Pension Fund, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Union Trustees of the NMU Pension Fund v. Employer Trustees of the NMU Pension Fund, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry, Local 730 v. Trane Company, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - United Automobile Workers (UAW), Local 365 v. Eagle Electric Manufacturing (2 cases), undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - UAW, Local 365 v. Kason Hardware Corp. (2 cases), undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - UAW, Local 265 v. Mergenthaler Linotype Co., undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 2682 v. Levin Fixture Corp., undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers (UFCW), Local 1500 v. Dairy Barn Stores, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - UFCW, Local 1 v. Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co., undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - UFCW, Local 174 v. Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co., undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - UFCW, Local 888 v. Greater NY Plumbing and Heating Supply Jobbers Association, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - UFCW, Local 1500 v. Gristedes Supermarkets, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - UFCW, Local 888 v. Hartz Mountain Corp., undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - UFCW, Local 342-50 v. Pathmark Stores, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - United Optical Workers' Union, Local 408 v. Sterling Optical, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - United Papermakers and Paperworkers Union, Local 712 v. Reigel Products Corp., undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - United Paperworkers International Union, Local 420 v. Fort Orange Paper, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - United Paperworkers International Union, Local 1712 v. Riegel Products Corp., undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - United Paperworkers International Union, Local 1066 v. Schoeller Technical Papers, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - United Paperworkers International Union, Local 3 v. United Merchants and Manufacturers, Inc., undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - United Paperworkers International Union, Local 1340 v. Westvaco, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - United Plant Guard Workers of America, Local 562 v. Burns International Security Services, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - United Seafood Workers, Local 359 v. M. Slavin and Sons, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. v. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1014, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. v. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1066 (3 cases), undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. v. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5030 (4 cases), undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. v. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5092 (8 cases), undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. v. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7246, undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - United Steelworkers of America, Local 12781 v. Allied Chemical Co. (2 cases), undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - United Steelworkers of America, Local 7853 v. Altoona Plant of Veeder-Root Co., undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - United Steelworkers of America, Local 6607 v. Continental Group (2 cases), undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - United Steelworkers of America, Local 16031 v. Gorham Co., undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - United Steelworkers of America, Local 5652 v. Metropolitan Wire Corp., undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - United Steelworkers of America, Local 837 v. U.S. Metals Refining Co., undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - United Steelworkers of America, Upholstery and Allied Division, Local 44 v. Guido De Angelis "L" and Sons, Inc., undated (Box 11, Folder 46a)
  - United Storeworkers Union v. Bloomingdale's, undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - United Storeworkers Union, Local #2 v. Gimbel Brothers, undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - United Transportation Union v. Long Island Railroad Co. (4 cases), undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - United Transportation Union v. Norfolk and Western Railroad Co., undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - United University Professions, Inc. v. SUNY Brockport, undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - United University Professions, Inc. v. SUNY Buffalo, undated (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - United University Professions, Inc. v. SUNY Genesco, undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - United University Professions, Inc. v. SUNY Old Westbury, undated (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Utility Workers Union of America, Local 374 v. Jamaica Water Supply Co., undated (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Veterans Administrative Medical Center v. American Federation of Government Employees, Local 2094, undated (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Vick, Joseph (AFSCME, Council #82) v. NY State Department of Correctional Services, undated (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Wassaic Developmental Center v. Kluglein, Mary (1 of 2), undated (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Wassaic Developmental Center v. Kluglein, Mary (2 of 2), undated (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Whitestone General Hospital v. SEIU, Local 144, undated (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Whitley, Rexa (CSEA) v. NY State Department of Mental Hygeine, undated (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Wholesale, Retail, Office, and Processing Union, District #65 v. Royal London, Ltd., undated (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Wire Service Guild, Local 22 v. Associated Press, undated (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Wire Service Guild, Local 222 v. Associated Press, undated (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Wire Service Guild, Local 222 v. United Press International, undated (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Wurm, Jesse v. Trans World Airlines, undated (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Yeshiva University v. NYSNA, undated (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - National Mediation Board (Railroad Grievances): Public Law Board (NMB/PLB) 1685, Decisions 1-2, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - NMB/PLB 1178, Decisions 1-50, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NMB/PLB 1178, Decisions 51-100, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - NMB/PLB 1178, Decisions 101-150, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - NMB/PLB 1178, Decisions 151-200, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - NMB/PLB 1853, Decisions 1-20, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - NMB/PLB 2150, Decisions 1-8, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - NMB/PLB 2150, Decisions 14-44 (several missing), undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - NMB/PLB 2445, Decisions 1-50 (several missing), undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - NMB/PLB 2445, Decisions 1-9, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - NMB/PLB 2445, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - NMB/PLB 2563, Decision 1, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - NMB/PLB 3103: General Materials, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - NMB/PLB 3103: Decisions, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - NMB/PLB 4267: General Materials, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - NMB/PLB 4267: Cases 54-59, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - NMB/PLB 4267: Cases 60-64, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - NMB/PLB 4267: Cases 64 and 67, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - NMB/PLB 4267: Case 67, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - NMB: Special Board of Adjustment, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - NMB: Special Board of Adjustment, 784, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board (Second Division), undated (Box 12, Folder 22)